Guide to the Youth Document Durham and Durham Works Project Records, 1995-2008 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Interviews Series, 1995-2008 and undated, (53 boxes)
  - Summerton, S.C. Defee, Vernon. Summerton, S.C. Teacher, Principal. 1997 June 27 (Box 12, Folder 162)
  - Summerton, S.C. Bowman, Kennita. Summerton, S.C. High School Student. 1997 July 19 (Box 13, Folder 163)
  - Summerton, S.C. Watson, Jackie. Summerton, S.C. 1997 July 1 (Box 13, Folder 164)
  - Summerton, S.C. Gates, Marie. Summerton, S.C. 1997 July 19 (Box 13, Folder 165)
  - Summerton, S.C. McDonald, Mary. Summerton, S.C. 1997 July 1 (Box 13, Folder 166)
  - Summerton, S.C. Singleton, Joe. Orangeburg. Teacher, Principal. 1997 July 10 (Box 13, Folder 167)
  - Summerton, S.C. Session, Ellanora. Summerton, S.C. Reading Aide. 1997 July 11 (Box 13, Folder 168)
  - Summerton, S.C. Brunson, Harold. Columbia. Principal. 1997 June 30 (Box 13, Folder 169)
  - Summerton, S.C. Spry, Carrie. Summerton, S.C. Teacher. 1997 July 15 (Box 13, Folder 170)
  - Summerton, S.C. Jackson, Ohilian. Summerton, S.C. 1997 July 21 (Box 13, Folder 171)
  - Wilson. Jones, Mary. Wilson. 1997 July 18 (Box 14, Folder 172)
  - Behind the Veil. Saunders, Ameilia. Pinewood. Maid. 1995 July 9 (Box 14, Folder 173)
  - Behind the Veil. Watson, Netta. Summerton, S.C. Teachers Aide, Farmer, Waitress. 1995 July 7 (Box 14, Folder 174)
  - Mercy Hospital. Lewis, Daphine. Wilson. Nurses Aide. 1996 July 29 (Box 14, Folder 175)
  - Behind the Veil. Parks, Leola. Manning. Instructional Assistant, Secretary. 1995 July 6 (Box 14, Folder 176)
  - Behind the Veil. Miller, Jarrett. Davis Station. Farmer. 1995 Sept. 7 (Box 14, Folder 177)
  - Behind the Veil. Mooler, Idella. Summerton, S.C. Teachers Aide. 1997 July 11 (Box 14, Folder 178)
  - Behind the Veil. Mellerson, Queen. Manning. 1995 July 5 (Box 14, Folder 179)
  - Behind the Veil. Levy, Moses. Summerton, S.C. Mason, Farmer. 1995 July 9 (Box 14, Folder 180)
  - Behind the Veil. Bennett, Charles. Summerton, S.C. (Box 14, Folder 181)
  - Behind the Veil. Banks, Louise. Summerton, S.C. (Box 14, Folder 182)
  - Mercy Hospital. Thornton, Jacqueline. Durham. 1996 June 24 (Box 14, Folder 183)
  - Mercy Hospital. Fester, Alpha. Wilson. 1996 June 24 (Box 14, Folder 184)
  - Everette, Mattie. Durham. 1997 June 9 (Box 15, Folder 185)
  - Behind the Veil. Brailsford, Julia Mae. Pinewood. 1995 July 9 (Box 15, Folder 186)
  - Mercy Hospital. Brooks, Victor. Wilson. 1996 June 24 (Box 15, Folder 187)
  - Student Practice. Kirby, Brenda. Wilson. Teaching Assistant. 1996 June 20 (Box 15, Folder 188)
  - Student Practice. Hodges, Wayne. Wilson. 1996 June 20 (Box 15, Folder 189)
  - Behind the Veil. Levy, Lucille. Summerton, S.C. 1996 June 20 (Box 15, Folder 190)
  - Student Practice. Gardner, Horteuse. Wilson. 1996 June 20 (Box 15, Folder 191)
  - Mercy Hospital. Burks, Gloria. Wilson. Retired Teacher. 1996 June 26 (Box 15, Folder 192)
  - Wilson. Farmer, Verna. Wilson. 1997 July 11 (Box 15, Folder 193)
  - Wilson. Moore, Mary. Wilson. 1997 July 17 (Box 15, Folder 194)
  - Wilson. Jones, Doris. Wilson. 1997 July 24 (Box 15, Folder 195)
  - Behind the Veil. Detany, Blendall. Summerton, S.C. 1995 July 6 (Box 16, Folder 196)
  - Wilson. Corbett, Fannie. Wilson. 1997 July 14 (Box 16, Folder 197)
  - [Folder 198 is missing.] (Box 16)
  - Wilson. Moore, Beatrice. Wilson. 1997 July 9 (Box 16, Folder 199)
  - Wilson. Brunson, Dorothy. Wilson. 1997 July 21 (Box 16, Folder 200)
  - Wilson. Barnes, Clarence. Wilson. 1997 July 21 (Box 16, Folder 201)
  - Wilson. Reid, Anthony. Wilson. 1997 July 23 (Box 16, Folder 202)
  - Wilson. Perry, Annie and Joesph Jr. Wilson. 1997 July 14 (Box 16, Folder 203)
  - Wilson. Braswell, Doris. Wilson. 1997 July 21 (Box 16, Folder 204)
  - Weaver, Otis. 1997 July 21 (Box 16, Folder 205)
  - Wilson. Sharpe, J.D. Wilson. Teacher. 1997 July 21 (Box 17, Folder 206)
  - Wilson. Lewis, Cleveland. Wilson. Retired Teacher. 1997 July 21 (Box 17, Folder 207)
  - Student Practice. Woodard, JoAnne. Wilson. 1996 June 20 (Box 17, Folder 208)
  - Summerton, S.C. Cantey, Lethia. Summerton, S.C. 1997 June 30 (Box 17, Folder 209)
  - Summerton, S.C. Drayton, Mary. Rimini. 7-14-9? (Box 17, Folder 210)
  - Summer Training. Smith, Herbert. Durham. 1997 June 9 (Box 17, Folder 211)
  - Summer Training. Greene, Willie. 1997 June 9 (Box 17, Folder 212)
  - Behind the Veil. Doctor-Wearing, Alice. Summerton, S.C. 1996 June 11 (Box 17, Folder 213)
  - Durham's West End. Richmond, Barbara. Durham. 1997 July 16 (Box 17, Folder 214)
  - Old Five Points. Little, Mabel. Durham. 1997 July 11 (Box 17, Folder 215)
  - Mercy Hospital. Hardy, Tom. Wilson. Teacher. 1996 June 24 (Box 18, Folder 216)
  - Summer Training. McLester, Johny. Durham. 1997 June 9 (Box 18, Folder 217)
  - Summer Training. Chandler, Janette. Summerton, S.C. 1996 June 11 (Box 18, Folder 218)
  - Behind the Veil. Parker, Loreatha. Durham. Teacher. 1996 June 12 (Box 18, Folder 219)
  - Old Five Points. Parker, Robert. Greensboro. Student. 1997 June 24 (Box 18, Folder 220)
  - Lawson, Idella. 1995 July 3 (Box 18, Folder 221)
  - King, Luela. 1997 July 7 (Box 18, Folder 222)
  - Hadon, Fannie. 1992 July 2 (Box 18, Folder 223)
  - Old Five Points. Green, Nichole. Durham. 1997 June 24 (Box 18, Folder 224)
  - Patterson, Annie. (Box 18, Folder 225)
  - Tobacco Talk. Smith, Adell. Durham. Farmer. 1998 July 23 (Box 18, Folder 226)
  - Crest Street/Old Five Points. Battle, Betty. Durham. 1997 July 2 and 21 (Box 19, Folder 227)
  - Atamai, 1997 July 7 (Box 19, Folder 228)
  - Artis, Vera. 1996 July 25 (Box 19, Folder 229)
  - Booth, Josephine and William. Durham. 1997 July 23 (Box 19, Folder 230)
  - Brown, James. 1997 July 29 (Box 19, Folder 231)
  - [Folder 232 is missing.] (Box 19)
  - Behind the Veil. Ford, Dorthea. Surbyville. Teacher. 1996 June 21 (Box 19, Folder 233)
  - Gamble, Delia. 1996 June 24 (Box 19, Folder 234)
  - Wilson. Coleman, Avant. Wilson. Clerk Agent. 1997 July 21 (Box 19, Folder 235)
  - Richardson, Blandell. 1995 July 6 (Box 20, Folder 236)
  - Richburg, Shondra. 1996 June 19 (Box 20, Folder 237)
  - Summerton, S.C. Rivers, Mr. and Mrs. Lawrence. Capitol Heights. 1997 June 29 (Box 20, Folder 238)
  - Durham's West End. McNeil, Juanita. Durham. Utility Specialist. 1997 July 20 (Box 20, Folder 239)
  - Durham's West End. Webb, Arlene. Durham. Nurse. 1997 July 15 (Box 20, Folder 240)
  - Behind the Veil. Watts, Charles. Durham. Doctor. 1996 June 12 (Box 20, Folder 241)
  - Victoria, Olivia. 1997 July 10 (Box 20, Folder 242)
  - Tillie, Chakila. 1996 June 19 (Box 20, Folder 243)
  - Taylor, James. 1997 July 18 (Box 20, Folder 244)
  - Brunson, Harold. 1996 July 20 (Box 21, Folder 245)
  - Durham's West End. Byrd, Virginia. Durham, West End. 1997 July 16 (Box 21, Folder 246)
  - Tobacco Talk. Stevens, Alfreida. Social Worker. 1998 July 10 (Box 21, Folder 247)
  - Tobacco Talk. Stevens, Alfreida. (Box 21, Folder 247)
  - Summerton, S.C. Hall, Barbara. Davis Station. Social Worker. 1996 July 7 (Box 21, Folder 248)
  - Summerton, S.C. Harvin, George. Manning. 1996 July 6 (Box 21, Folder 249)
  - Old Five Points. Wilson, Veronica. Durham. Housekeeper. 1997 July 25 (Box 21, Folder 250)
  - Old Five Points. Young, Gussie. Durham. Construction. 1997 July 14 (Box 21, Folder 251)
  - Old Five Points. Jenkins, James. Durham. 1997 July 25 (Box 21, Folder 252)
  - Old Five Points. Lowery, Lueisa. Durham. Housekeeper. 7-3 and 7-8-97 (Box 21, Folder 253)
  - Old Five Points. Cannady, Mary. Durham. 1997 July 10 (Box 22, Folder 254)
  - Old Five Points. Woyee, Annie. Durham, Old Five Points. 1997 July 3 (Box 22, Folder 255)
  - Old Five Points. Poole, Ruth. Durham. 1997 July 30 (Box 22, Folder 256)
  - West End. Wiley, Johnnie. Durham, West End. Lab Technician. 1997 July 16 (Box 22, Folder 257)
  - West End. Belk, Johnnie. Durham, West End. 1997 July 10 (Box 22, Folder 259)
  - Mercy Hospital. Barrett, Mary. Wilson. Department Store Employee. 1996 June 26 (Box 22, Folder 260)
  - Old Five Points. Fuguay, Geraldine. Durham, North Durham. 1997 July 11 (Box 22, Folder 261)
  - Summerton, S.C. Richardson, Chaney. Summerton, S.C. Field worker. 1997 June 26 (Box 22, Folder 262)
  - Summerton, S.C. Johnson, Inez. Summerton, S.C. Teacher. 1995 July 9 (Box 23, Folder 263)
  - Crest Street. Gattis, Meadell. Durham, Crest Street. Nurse. 1997 July 21 (Box 23, Folder 264)
  - Wilson. Buchanan, James. Wilson. Teacher. 1997 July 23 (Box 23, Folder 265)
  - Old Five Points. Gladden, Fannie. Durham, Old Five Points. Beautician, Retail Salesperson. 1997 July 7 (Box 23, Folder 266)
  - Behind the Veil. Washington, James. Summerton, S.C. Tool mechanic. 1995 July 11 (Box 23, Folder 267)
  - Wilson. Whitted, Bessie. Wilson. Nurse. 1996 July 19 (Box 23, Folder 268)
  - Mercy Hospital. Woodard, JoAnne. Wilson. Psychologist, Therapist, Professor. 1996 July 12 (Box 23, Folder 269)
  - Tobacco Talk. Elliott, Mary. Durham, West End. Seamstress, Baker, Tobacco Worker. (Box 23, Folder 270)
  - Tobacco Talk. Watson, George. Durham, West End. 1998 July 23 (Box 24, Folder 271)
  - Tobacco Talk. Scarborough, John, III. Durham. Mortician. (Box 24, Folder 272)
  - Tobacco Talk. McKee, Etta. Durham. 1998 July 27 (Box 24, Folder 273)
  - Tobacco Talk. McNeil, Juanita. Durham, West End. Teacher. 1998 June 30 (Box 24, Folder 274)
  - Tobacco Talk. Davis, Matthew. Durham. Tobacco Worker. 1998 July 12 (Box 24, Folder 275)
  - SWCD. Googe, Iris. Durham, West End. Housekeeper. 1998 July 22 (Box 24, Folder 276)
  - SWCD. McKee, Etta. Durham, West End. Teacher. 1998 July 13 (Box 24, Folder 277)
  - SWCD. Walker, Frank. Durham. Minister. 1998 July 28 (Box 24, Folder 278)
  - SWCD. Rogers, Jerry. Durham. 1998 July 15 (Box 24, Folder 280)
  - SWCD. Richmond, Barbara. Durham. Accountant. 1998 July 20 (Box 24, Folder 281)
  - SWCD. Samuel, James, Jr. Durham. Manager. 1998 July 13 (Box 25, Folder 282)
  - SWCD. Carrington, Bessie. Durham. Librarian. 1998 July 12 (Box 25, Folder 283)
  - SWCD. Smith, Bessie. Durham, West End. Homemaker. 1998 July 17 (Box 25, Folder 284)
  - SWCD. Brogdon, Helen. Durham. 1998 July 29 (Box 25, Folder 285)
  - Tobacco Talk. Harris, Iris. Durham. AIDS Hotline Receptionist. 1998 July 29 (Box 25, Folder 286)
  - Summer Training. Holman, Julia. Durham, Crest Street. 1998 June 5 (Box 25, Folder 287)
  - Summer Training. Scurlock, Ila. Durham, Crest Street. 1998 June 5 (Box 25, Folder 288)
  - SWCD. Kearney, Gloria. Durham. Nurse. 1998 July 15 (Box 25, Folder 289)
  - SWCD. Smith, Ellis. Durham. 1998 July 19 (Box 25, Folder 290)
  - SWCD. Webb, Betsy. Durham. Administrative Clerk. 1998 July 20 (Box 25, Folder 291)
  - SWCD. Webb, Mae. Durham. 1998 July 26 (Box 26, Folder 292)
  - SWCD. Gill, Judy. Durham. 1998 July 29 (Box 26, Folder 293)
  - Old Five Points. McCuller, Wavney. Durham. 1997 July 3 (Box 26, Folder 294)
  - Crest Street. Scarlett, Larry. Lithonia. Special Agent for US Department of Agriculture. 1997 July 6 (Box 26, Folder 295)
  - Faith Stories. Dworsky, Leon. Durham. Freelance Computer Programmer. 1998 June 23 (Box 26, Folder 296)
  - Crest Street. Johnson, Nathaniel. Durham, Crest Street. Pressman. 1997 July 1 (Box 26, Folder 298)
  - Crest Street. Johnson, Fred. Durham, Crest Street. 1997 July 6 (Box 26, Folder 299)
  - Summerton, S.C. Levy, Moses. Manning. 1996 June 11 (Box 26, Folder 300)
  - Old Five Points. Smith, Callina. Durham. 1997 July 9 (Box 27, Folder 301)
  - Old Five Points. Satterfield, Betty. Durham, Old Five Points. Nurse. 1997 July 3 (Box 27, Folder 302)
  - Old Five Points. Alston, Margaret. Durham. 1997 July 3 (Box 27, Folder 303)
  - Old Five Points. Greene, Charity. Durham, Old Five Points. 1997 July 31 (Box 27, Folder 304)
  - Old Five Points. Dunham, Charles. Durham. 1997 July 9 (Box 27, Folder 305)
  - Behind the Veil. Brailsford, Carrie. Summerton, S.C. Housekeeper. 1995 June 30 (Box 27, Folder 307)
  - Crest Street. Odom, Hilda. Durham, Crest Street. Lab. Technician. 1997 July 19 (Box 27, Folder 309)
  - Crest Street. McMillan, Garry. Durham, Crest Street. 1998 July 30 (Box 27, Folder 311)
  - Crest Street. Nunn, Wilbert. Durham, Crest Street. 1998 July 24 (Box 27, Folder 312)
  - Crest Street. Yarborough, Anita. Durham, Crest Street. Healthcare Worker. 1998 July 5 (Box 28, Folder 313)
  - Crest Street. Patterson, Willie. Durham. 1998 July 2 (Box 28, Folder 314)
  - Crest Street. Holman, Julia. Durham, Crest Street. 1998 July 14 (Box 28, Folder 315)
  - Tobacco Talk. Phillips, Senora. Durham. Farmer. 1998 July 19 (Box 28, Folder 316)
  - Tobacco Talk. Moore, Thelma. Durham. Department Store Employee, Tobacco Worker. 1998 July 26 (Box 28, Folder 317)
  - Tobacco Talk. Woodard, Annie. Durham, Hearthside. 1998 July 28 (Box 28, Folder 318)
  - Crest Street. Odom, Hilda. Durham, Crest Street. Lab. Technician. 1998 July 18 (Box 28, Folder 319)
  - Crest Street. Holloway, Emmer. Durham, Crest Street. 1998 July 9 (Box 28, Folder 320)
  - Crest Street. Patterson, Charlotte. Durham, Crest Street. 1998 July 19 (Box 28, Folder 321)
  - Crest Street. Lowe, Lula. Durham, Crest Street. 1998 July 26 (Box 28, Folder 322)
  - Crest Street. Johnson, Betty. Durham, Crest Street. Elementary School Teacher, Counselor, City Planner. 1998 July 29 (Box 28, Folder 323)
  - Crest Street. Henderson, Wanda. Durham, Crest Street. Retirement Home Employee. 1998 July 2 (Box 28, Folder 324)
  - Crest Street. Winston, Marie. Durham, Crest Street. 1998 July 20 (Box 28, Folder 325)
  - Crest Street. Pratt, Nathaniel. Durham, Crest Street. 1998 July 9 (Box 29, Folder 326)
  - Crest Street. Scarlet, Reta. Durham, Crest Street. 1998 July 17 (Box 29, Folder 327)
  - Crest Street. Holloway, Mary. Durham, Crest Street. 1998 July 9 (Box 29, Folder 328)
  - Crest Street. Cooper, Mary. Durham, Crest Street. 1998 July 14 (Box 29, Folder 329)
  - Crest Street. Battle, Betty. Durham, Crest Street. 1998 July 7 (Box 29, Folder 330)
  - Crest Street. Johnson, Felicia. Durham Crest Street. 1998 July 28 (Box 29, Folder 331)
  - Crest Street. Brown, James. Durham, Crest Street. 1998 July 13 (Box 29, Folder 332)
  - Crest Street. Smith, Adrian. Durham, Crest Street. 1998 July 28 (Box 29, Folder 333)
  - Crest Street. Elliot, Luvenia. Durham, Crest Street. 1998 July 30 (Box 29, Folder 334)
  - Crest Street. Nunn, Edgar. Durham, Crest Street. 1998 July 23 (Box 29, Folder 335)
  - Crest Street. Calloway, Jesse. Durham, Crest Street. 1998 July 9 (Box 29, Folder 336)
  - Faith Stories. Barnette, Toinne. Durham. Fleet Service Clerk at RDU, Water Fitness Instructor, Nurse Interim, Museum Educator. 1998 June 29 (Box 29, Folder 337)
  - Faith Stories. Abdul-Salaam, Karen. Durham. Accountant. 1998 July 7 (Box 29, Folder 338)
  - Faith Stories. Brennan, Corey. Durham. Ministerial Intern, Student. 1998 June 24 (Box 30, Folder 339)
  - Faith Stories. Silverstein, Elliot. Chapel Hill. Psychiatrist, Professor. 1998 July 8 (Box 30, Folder 340)
  - Young, Mamie. Durham. 1998 July 13 (Box 30, Folder 341)
  - Tobacco Talk. Bostic, Charles. Durham. 1998 July 22 (Box 30, Folder 342)
  - SWCD. Carroll, Cheryl. Durham. Nurse. 1998 July 24 (Box 30, Folder 343)
  - SWCD. Bynum, Ernestine. Durham, West End. Teacher's Aide, Secretary. 1998 July 23 (Box 30, Folder 344)
  - Faith Stories. Klopfer, Peter. Durham. Professor. 1998 July 30 (Box 30, Folder 345)
  - Faith Stories. Davis, Glenn. Durham. Minister. 1998 June 23 (Box 30, Folder 346)
  - SWCD. Cassell, Harry. Durham. Cook. 1998 Aug. 3 (Box 30, Folder 347)
  - SWCD. Alston, Lillian. Chapel Hill. Day Care Center Employee. 1998 Aug. 2 (Box 30, Folder 348)
  - SWCD. Perry, Frankie. Durham. Bank Trust Officer, Teacher. 1998 July 14 (Box 31, Folder 349)
  - Tobacco Talk. Quick, Delores. Durham. Housewife. 1998 July 30 (Box 31, Folder 350)
  - SWCD. Harris, Barbara. Durham. 1998 Aug. 2 (Box 31, Folder 351)
  - SWCD. Minor, James. Durham. Cook. 1998 July 13 (Box 31, Folder 352)
  - SWCD. Lindsay, Virginia. Durham. Custodian, Nursing Assistant. 1998 July 16 (Box 31, Folder 353)
  - SWCD. Joiner, William. Durham. 1998 July 28 (Box 31, Folder 354)
  - SWCD. Jackson, Gertrude. Durham. 1998 Aug. 3 (Box 31, Folder 355)
  - Old Five Points. Carter, Valerie. Durham. 1997 July 22 (Box 31, Folder 356)
  - Old Five Points. McKever, Kim. Durham, Old Five Points. Duke Children's Hospital Employee. 1997 July 3 (Box 31, Folder 357)
  - Old Five Points. Beason, Matthew. Durham. Student. 1997 June 24 (Box 31, Folder 358)
  - Old Five Points. Greene, Tamaira. Durham. 1997 June 24 (Box 31, Folder 359)
  - Old Five Points. Smith, Horace. Durham. 1997 July 16 (Box 31, Folder 360)
  - Old Five Points. Everette, Eloise and Arthur. Durham, Old Five Points. Minister, Contractor. 1997 July 3 (Box 32, Folder 361)
  - Wilson. Pridgen, Marion, Jr. Wilson. Tobacco Farmer. 1997 July 14 (Box 32, Folder 362)
  - Wilson. Jones, Edward. Wilson. Migrant Tobacco Worker. 1997 July 17 (Box 32, Folder 363)
  - Wilson. Hoskins, Clarence. Wilson. Tobacco Worker, Vocational Instructor. 1997 July 11 (Box 32, Folder 364)
  - Wilson. Creech, Delores. Wilson. Tobacco Worker. 1997 July 9 (Box 32, Folder 365)
  - Wilson. Hoskins, Ernestine. Wilson. Tobacco Worker, Healthcare Worker. 1997 July 22 (Box 32, Folder 366)
  - Tobacco Talk. Warren, Linda. Durham. 1998 July 21 (Box 32, Folder 367)
  - SWCD. Merritt, Carl. Durham, Lyon Park. 1997 July 17 (Box 32, Folder 368)
  - Durham's West End. Brown, Alice. Durham, West End. 1997 July 18 (Box 32, Folder 369)
  - Durham's West End. Walker, Constance. Durham, West End. Lawyer, Adjustor for Durham Public Schools. 1997 July 16 (Box 32, Folder 370)
  - Durham's West End. Sartor, Elizabeth. Durham. 1997 July 16 (Box 32, Folder 371)
  - Durham's West End. Roberson, Florine. Durham. 1997 July 16 (Box 32, Folder 372)
  - Durham's West End. Woods, Thelma. Durham, West End. 1997 July 11 (Box 32, Folder 373)
  - Durham's West End. Keith, Mable. Durham. Nursing Assistant. 1997 July 16 (Box 32, Folder 374)
  - Faith Stories. Muhammad, Abdullah. Durham. City Planner. 1998 July 7 and 26 (Box 33, Folder 375)
  - Faith Stories. Patterson, Kathy. Durham. 1998 July 7 (Box 33, Folder 376)
  - Faith Stories. Muhammad, Abdur-Rashid. Durham. Furniture Employee, Self-Employed. 1998 July 27 (Box 33, Folder 377)
  - Faith Stories. Marrow, Greg. Durham. 1998 July 29 (Box 33, Folder 378)
  - Faith Stories. Miller, Mary. Durham. 1998 July 7 and 28 (Box 33, Folder 379)
  - Faith Stories. Gavin, Linda. Durham. Cook. 1998 June 29 (Box 33, Folder 380)
  - Faith Stories. Muhammad, Ni’mat. Durham, Lakewood Park. Administrative Clerk. 1998 June 28 (Box 33, Folder 381)
  - Faith Stories. Reed, Sam. Durham. Labor Activist. 1998 July 27 (Box 33, Folder 382)
  - Faith Stories. Odom, Hilda. Durham, Crest Street. Lab. Technician, Research Associate. 1998 July 7 (Box 34, Folder 383)
  - Faith Stories. O’Connor, Bill. Durham. Middle School Teacher. 1998 July 12 (Box 34, Folder 384)
  - Mercy Hospital. Harris, Eula. Wilson. 1996 July 27 (Box 34, Folder 385)
  - Mercy Hospital. Hutcherson, Essie. Wilson. 1996 July 30 (Box 34, Folder 386)
  - Mercy Hospital. Atkinson, Maggie. Wilson. 1996 July 24 (Box 34, Folder 387)
  - Tobacco Talk. McKee, Etta. Durham, West End. Teacher. 1997 July 27 (Box 34, Folder 388)
    No documentation in file, single interview tape only. Refer to files 273 and 277 that contain additional interviews of Etta McKee.
  - [Interview folders 389-399 are missing.] (Box 34)
  - Durham Eats. (Box 34, Folder 400)
  - Durham Eats. Olave, Katushka. 2000 July 17 (Box 35, Folder 401)
  - Durham Eats. Atwater, Will. 2000 July 20 (Box 35, Folder 402)
  - Durham Eats. Washington, Sandee. 2000 July 11 (Box 35, Folder 403)
  - Durham Eats. Eckert, Mark. 2000 July 11 (Box 35, Folder 404)
  - Community Stories. West End Langely, Vernon.1999 (Box 35, Folder 405)
  - Community Stories. West End Googe, Iris. 1998 June 1 (Box 35, Folder 406)
  - Community Stories. West End Langley, Angela.1999 (Box 35, Folder 407)
  - Community Stories. West End Smith-Adams, Keely. Physician's Assistant.1999 (Box 35, Folder 408)
  - Community Stories. Bea.1999 (Box 36, Folder 409)
  - Community Stories. West End Perry, Frankie. (Box 36, Folder 410)
  - Community Stories. West End O’Neal, Elton. (Box 36, Folder 410)
  - Community Stories. Mckinney, Charles. (Box 36, Folder 411)
  - Durham Eats. Anglin, Peggy. (Box 36, Folder 412)
  - Harman, Linda. (Box 36, Folder 413)
  - Durham Eats. Toomer, Gwen. (Box 36, Folder 414)
  - Durham Eats. Maple Farm Dairy Dairy Farmer. 2000 Summer (Box 36, Folder 415)
  - Crime Beat. Watkins, Francis. Attorney. 2000 June 14 (Box 36, Folder 416)
  - Crime Beat. Arceo, Ramro. 2000 June 14 (Box 36, Folder 417)
  - Crime Beat. Brown, Craig. Judge. 2000 June 15 (Box 37, Folder 418)
  - Crime Beat. Wagstaff, Jackie. City Councilwoman. (Box 37, Folder 419)
  - Crime Beat. Davis, Deborah. Secretary at NE Central Durham Community Service Center. 2000 June 20 (Box 37, Folder 420)
  - Youth Document Durham. Abdusamad, Karima. (Box 37, Folder 421)
  - Youth Document Durham. Chahine, Fadi. (Box 37, Folder 422)
  - Youth Document Durham. Page, Jack. Doctor. (Box 37, Folder 423)
  - Techno-Durham. Chahine, Priscilla and Fadi. (Box 37, Folder 424)
  - Youth Document Durham. Smith, Bob. 2000 July 12 (Box 37, Folder 425)
  - Youth Document Durham. Reid, Roxanne. (Box 37, Folder 426)
  - Durham Works. Navies, Kelly. Poet. 2000 Apr. 15 (Box 37, Folder 427)
  - Durham Works. Marshall, Janie. Nurse in Children’s Emergency Dept. 2000 Apr. 20 (Box 38, Folder 428)
  - Durham Works. Simonette, Rick. Employee at RPM Nissan. 2000 Apr. 19 (Box 38, Folder 429)
  - Durham Works. Ganet, Friesh. Employee at Blue Nile. 2000 Apr. 19 (Box 38, Folder 429)
  - Durham Works.TriangleCitySearch.com 2000 Apr. 12 (Box 38, Folder 430)
  - Durham Works. Borges, Hector. Police Officer. 2000 Apr. 12 (Box 38, Folder 431)
  - Durham Works. Barbee, Natasha. Cosmetologist. 2000 Apr. 18 (Box 38, Folder 432)
  - Durham Works. Kettle, Tom. Wrestler. 2000 Apr. 22 (Box 38, Folder 433)
  - Durham Works. Cornell, Jeff. Actor. 2000 May 2 (Box 38, Folder 434)
  - Durham Works. Lawes. Cosmetologist. 2000 May 11 (Box 38, Folder 435)
  - Durham Works. Romano, John. Web Designer. 2000 May 15 (Box 38, Folder 436)
  - Durham Works. Banks, Sherrod. Lawyer. 2000 May 18 (Box 39, Folder 437)
  - Durham Works. Hill, Willie. Musician. 2000 May 12 (Box 39, Folder 438)
  - Sounds of the City. McKnight, David. 2000 June 21 (Box 39, Folder 439)
  - Community Stories. Gamble, Terri. (Box 39, Folder 440)
  - Techno-Durham. Britz, Greg. 2000 July 12 (Box 39, Folder 441)
  - Techno-Durham. Hofraker, Richard. 2000 June 13 (Box 39, Folder 442)
  - Durham Works. Freelon, Phil. 2000 May 9 (Box 39, Folder 443)
  - Durham Works. Barbee, Natasha. Durham. Cosmetologist. 2000 Nov. 9 (Box 39, Folder 444)
  - Durham Works. Tew, Cameron. Durham. Newspaper Editor. 2000 Nov. 1 (Box 39, Folder 445)
  - Durham Works. Eaton, Rebecca. Durham. News Reporter. 2000 Nov. 1 (Box 39, Folder 445)
  - Durham Works. Durham, Shawn. Durham. News Reporter. 2000 Nov. 1 (Box 39, Folder 445)
  - Durham Works. Taylor, Ross. Durham. News Photographer. 2000 Nov. 1 (Box 39, Folder 445)
  - Durham Works. Potter, Mike. Durham. Sports Writer. 2000 Nov. 29 (Box 40, Folder 446)
  - Durham Works. Spense, Phil. Durham. Basketball Coach. 2000 Nov. 20 (Box 40, Folder 446)
  - Durham Works. Perry, Kendric. Durham. Basketball Player. 2000 Nov. 29 (Box 40, Folder 446)
  - Durham Works. Vasquez, Laurie. Durham. Athletic Trainer. 2000 Nov. 29 (Box 40, Folder 446)
  - Durham Works. Hay-Merrill, Kathy. Durham. Thoracic Center Coordinator. 2000 Nov. 29 (Box 40, Folder 447)
  - Durham Works. Lowers, Christine. Durham. Gemologist. 2000 Nov. 16 (Box 40, Folder 448)